Joseph Marks-Chadwick

4479303333307	J
Joemarkschadwick@outlook.com	Y
https:/www.linkedin.com/in/josep	in
h-marks-chadwick-8b17ba116	
https://twitter.com/oddjoe_	#

I am a creative person, with a lot of ideas. Ever since I joined Club Penguin in 2006, I have had a passion for creating video games. I want to make an impact; the same way games have impacted my life. I love to create and innovate as there is nothing better than seeing something you have made come to life and enjoyed by so many people.

Skills

- 9+ years of using Adobe Flash/Animate
- 10+ years of using Adobe Photoshop
- 1+ years of using Evernote to plan and organize
- Years of experience planning in game events, and a virtual item economy
- Experienced in creating design specifications and design documentation
- Qualified in Media Studies with a great understanding on video editing software and techniques
- I am able adapt to new software very quickly
- I am currently learning how to draw with my Wacom Cintiq

Experience

FEBRUARY 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2018

CPRewritten - General Project Manager

It was my job to plan every single content update for a growing fanbase. This included planning the parties and events, managing all catalogues, designing aspects of the game and leading other team members to produce the best content possible.

I had to use analytics and user feedback to make the content the best it possibly could've been, always putting in 100%, so the players weren't let down. During this time, I had to deal with a large workload due to a small team of four developers, this really tested my ability to create content while under a lot of pressure.

At times, I had to be resourceful and use pre-existing content and expand on that. Most of the clothing catalogue releases reused old penguin art, but would quite frequently have recolored items, which proved to be very popular. As we did not have the original model for creating brand new items.

I handled everything from interface design, narrative, core gameplay mechanics, events planning, the item economy, mascot visits and everything that was needed to ensure the players had as much fun as

possible. I oversaw all the content updates as they went through the initial prototype stages all the way up to the release. Quite frequently I would be working on the projects.

February 2018 - September 2018

Devon Cliffs Mini Market – Shop Assistant

During this time, I was saving for university, so I worked at the Devon Cliffs Mini Market as a shop assistant. My main roles were to aid the customers, work the tills and restock the shelves, while working with my colleagues as a team.

I also had additional roles which included managing the general income from the previous shift and making that money was not missing. I also worked with Microsoft Excel on occasional to make sure that all stock was accounted for.

There was a lot of trust with this role as I had to manage thousands of pounds in cash daily.

SEPTEMBER 2017 - JANUARY 2018

Argos – Stockroom Assistant

This seasonal job had me working in the stockroom of an Argos store located in a busy city centre. My roles were to take stock deliveries, pack away stock and send stock down to the main shop floor for click and collect.

This job really tested my ability to work under pressure as this was over the busy Christmas period and boxing day sales.

SEPTEMBER 2016 - DECEMBER 2016

JD Wetherspoon Pub - Floor Staff

Working at JD Wetherspoon I had many important roles to ensure that the guests had an enjoyable time with us. My roles included serving drinks, sending out food and making sure the pub was clean and tidy.

Education

SEPTEMBER 2010 – JUNE 2015

GCSE/ Exmouth Community College

I graduated with nine GCSEs including computer science, graphics design and media studies.

SEPTEMBER 2015 - MAY 2017

A-Level / Exmouth Community College

I graduated passing with A-Levels in Computer Science, Media Studies and IT

Games Design / Bournemouth University

I am currently taking this course to improve my abilities in areas such as the business of the gaming industry, story design, UI design and many other areas